<resources>
    <string name="app_name">PekoNews</string>
    <string name="title_home">Home</string>
    <string name="title_dashboard">Dashboard</string>
    <string name="title_notifications">Notifications</string>
    <string name="descrip_title">Far Cry 6 Release Date, System
        \nRequirements,Cast, Price,
        \nGameplay, Review, and More</string>
    <string name="top_news">Top News</string>
    <string name="popular_game">Popular game</string>
    <string name="paragraf1">Far Cry 6, the sixth main instalment in the Far Cry series, is all
set to release this week. Developed by Ubisoft Toronto, Far
Cry 6 will be available on Amazon Luna, Microsoft Windows, PlayStation 4, PlayStation 5, Xbox One, Xbox Series X/S, and
Stadia. In the game, you play as local guerrilla Dani Rojas
(Sean Rey/ Nisa Gunduz) who's trying to liberate the fictional
 island Yara, based on Cuba, from the grips of the dictator
Antón Castillo.</string>
    <string name="paragraf2">Yara is ruled with an iron hand by dictator Antón Castillo —
played by Giancarlo Esposito who you might remember as
Gus Fring from the popular American TV series Breaking
Bad. Life is hard for the Yarans and they desire to escape
to a better life. Castillo\'s policies have isolated Yara from
the rest of the world. Having lost his father in a revolution
60 years ago, Castillo grew up believing that his country
had been stolen from him. As an adult, he rode a populist
wave to power, by romanticising the pre-revolution Yara.</string>
    <string name="paragraf3">Played from a first person perspective, Far Cry 6 puts you in the
shoes of Dani Rajos (Sean Rey/ Nisa Gunduz), a local Yaran who
just wants to get away. But after witnessing a horrific crime, Dani
is driven into waging guerrilla warfare against Castillo. Ubisoft
Toronto went to Cuba to experience the culture, and to
speak with former guerrillas and their descendants.
Given the failures of Far Cry 5 in handling political material,
many are naturally worried if Far Cry 6 is setting foot in a
quagmire. On the surface, Ubisoft seems to be handling the
political themes better this time around. Far Cry 6
narrative director Navid Khavari has publicly acknowledged
that Far Cry 6 is a political game.</string>
    <string name="txt_trending_games">Trending Games</string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="top_title">The Difference Between Far Cry 6 and GTA 5 Graphics Is Astonishing</string>
    <string name="tentang">About Me</string>
    <string name="content_tentang">Full Time Graphic Designer who responsible for daily graphic design content for a medium-sized government institution. Worked regularly on graphic, data visualization, branding, and social media material. Top 10 on the Bandung Visualthon 2015: Infographic Competition. Developed 180+ graphic design projects (data visualizations, brand identity, infographics, social media contents) that increased brand implementation by 20%. </string>
</resources>